

MY CONTACT

Phone

+639206267775

Email

eugenetamidles@gmail.com

Address

A - 43 Nia Road Brgy Pinyahan, Quezon City

SKILLS

- Computer Maintenance
- Operating System
- Technical Support
- Remote Desktop
- Troubleshooting

REFERENCES

Chito Binghay

Foundever - Palawan I.T Supervisor 0966 339 8401

Jenny Sibongga

Foundever - Mandaluyong I.T Supervisor 09760327525

EUGENE L. TAMIDLES

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

ABOUT MYSELF

Highly motivated graduating student pursuing a Bachelor's degree in Information Technology with a passion for technical problem and problem-solving A curiosity-driven person, doing research about future potential technologies and exploring digital ways of finding income. A well-skilled professional intern in Sitel Group that can lead tasks and projects, especially in troubleshooting remotely and physically.

Having previous company experience gave me the advantage and edge to handle technical issues and support end-users.

EXPERIENCE

Foundever | 2022 - 2023

I.T Support - Intern

- Installing, configuring, maintaining, and troubleshooting devices as well as the Thin Clients.
- Operating systems and Microsoft Office products.
- Familiar with AZURE and other Information Technology related software tools.
- Maintain of Computer System and Installation of Devices and Software and Configuration.
- Assisting and Deploying materials for agents and clients, preparing / maintaining the port network on Data Server.
- Providing Technical Support to overall daily computer performance.

SM Hypermarket | May 2019 - Oct 2019

Bagger

- Bagging grocery items as customers check out.
- Loads purchased items into carts and may help patrons carry items outside the mall.
- Responsible for collecting grocery items not purchased and delivering them to stock clerks.

EDUCATION

College Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

Quezon City University

2018 - 2023

Senior High School **Major in Information Communication Technology**

Technical Vocational - ICT

ABE International Business College

2016 - 2018